printingblue.com 2012-11-04

# Privacy Policy

  * »  Banners
    * »  10 oz Vinyl Banners
    * »  12 oz Vinyl Banners
    * »  Custom Vinyl Banner
  * »  Business Cards
    * »  Folded Business Cards
    * »  Standard Business Cards
    * »  Custom Business Cards
  * »  Bookmarks
    * »  2 x 6 Bookmarks
    * »  3 x 7 Bookmarks
    * »  Custom Bookmarks
  * »  Booklets
    * »  8.5 x 11 Booklets
    * »  8.5 x 5.5 Booklets
    * »  Custom Booklets
  * »  Brochures
    * »  8.5 x 11 Brochures
    * »  8.5 x 14 Brochures
    * »  11 x 17 Brochures
    * »  Custom Brochure
  * »  Bottle Neckers
  * »  Carbonless Forms
    * »  2 Part Carbonless Forms
    * »  3 Part Carbonless Forms
    * »  4 Part Carbonless Forms
    * »  5 Part Carbonless Forms
    * »  Custom Carbonless Forms
  * »  CD Jackets
    * »  2 Panel CD Jackets
    * »  4 Panel CD Jackets
    * »  6 Panel CD Jackets
    * »  Custom CD jackets
  * »  CD Printing
  * »  Calendars
    * »  1 Page Calendar
    * »  6 Page Calendar
    * »  12-Page Calendars
    * »  Custom Calendars
  * »  Catalogs
    * »  8.5 x 11 Catalogs
    * »  8.5 x 5.5 Catalogs
    * »  Custom catalogs
  * »  Christmas Printing
    * »  Christmas Greeting Cards
    * »  Christmas Greeting Envelopes
    * »  Custom Christmas Printing
  * »  Clings
    * »  Auto Clings
    * »  Car Clings
    * »  Cling Decals
    * »  Cling Stickers
    * »  Custom Clings
    * »  Die-Cut Clings
    * »  Parking Clings
    * »  Round Clings
    * »  Vinyl Clings
    * »  Static Window Clings
    * »  Window Clings
  * »  Decals
    * »  Alarm Decals
    * »  Car Decals
    * »  Custom Decals
    * »  Custom Vinyl Decals
    * »  Decal Clings
    * »  Decal Stickers
    * »  Die-cut Vinyl Decals
    * »  Double Sided Decals
    * »  Outdoor Decals
    * »  Hard Hat Decals
    * »  Parking Decals
    * »  Round Decals
    * »  Vinyl Decals
  * »  Door Hangers
    * »  4 x 9 Door Hangers
    * »  5 x 8 Door Hangers
    * »  Baby Door Hangers
    * »  Business Door Hangers
    * »  Custom Door hangers
    * »  Do Not Disturb Door Hanger
    * »  Door Hanger Advertisement
    * »  Door Hanger Flyers
    * »  Full Color Door Hangers
    * »  Kids Door Hangers
    * »  Marketing Door Hangers
    * »  Paper Door Hangers
    * »  Political Door Hangers
    * »  Printable Door Hanager
    * »  Promotional Door Hangers
  * »  Envelopes
    * »  C6 Envelopes
    * »  DL Envelopes
    * »  # 10 Envelopes
    * »  # 9 Envelopes
    * »  9x12 Envelopes
    * »  Custom Envelopes
  * »  Flyers
    * »  4 x 6 Flyers
    * »  8.5 x 11 Flyers
    * »  Busienss Flyers
    * »  Club Card Flyers
    * »  Die Cut Flyers
    * »  Custom Flyers
  * »  Folders
    * »  6 x 9 Pocket Folders
    * »  9 x 12 Presentation Folders
    * »  9.5 x 14.5 Folders
    * »  Business Folders
    * »  Certificate holders
    * »  Embossed Folders
    * »  File Folders
    * »  Landscape Folders
    * »  Legal Sized folders
    * »  Letter Sized Folders
    * »  Pocket Folders
    * »  Portrait Folders
    * »  Presentation Folders
    * »  Tri Panel Folders
    * »  Tri-Panel Presentation Folders
    * »  Custom Folders
  * »  Greeting Cards
    * »  7 x 5 Greeting Cards
    * »  8.5 x 6 Greeting Cards
    * »  10 x 7 Greeting Cards
    * »  Personalized Greeting Cards
  * »  Invitational Cards
    * »  Anniversary Invitations
    * »  Bridal showers Invitations
    * »  Party Invitations
    * »  Custom Invitation Card
  * »  Labels
    * »  Bar Code Labels
    * »  Business Labels
    * »  Embossed Foil Labels
    * »  General Purpose Labels
    * »  Product Labels
    * »  Shipping Labels
    * »  Wine Labels
    * »  Custom Labels
  * »  Letterheads
    * »  8.5 x 11 Letter Heads
    * »  8.5 x 14 Letter Heads
    * »  Custom Letterheads
  * »  Logo Design
    * »  Bronze package
    * »  Gold package
    * »  Silver package
  * »  Magazines
    * »  8 Page magazines
    * »  12 page magazines
    * »  16 Page magazines
    * »  Custom Magazine Printing
  * »  Manuals
    * »  16 Page Manuals
    * »  8 Page Manuals
    * »  Custom Manual Printing
  * »  Mouse Pads
  * »  Mylar Bags
  * »  Newsletters
    * »  4 Page News Letters
    * »  8 Page News Letters
    * »  16 Page News Letters
    * »  Custom Newsletter
  * »  Packaging Boxes
    * »  Advertising Packaging
    * »  Bakery Cake Boxes
    * »  Beer Bottle Boxes
    * »  Beverage Packaging
    * »  Cigarette Boxes
    * »  Corrugated Boxes
    * »  Custom Packaging
  * »  Post Cards
    * »  4 x 6 Post Cards
    * »  5 x 7 Post Cards
    * »  5 x 8 Post Cards
    * »  6 x 9 Post Cards
    * »  Custom Postcards
  * »  Posters
    * »  11 x 17 posters
    * »  12.75 x 17.25 Posters
    * »  18 x 24 Posters
    * »  Custom Posters
  * »  Rack Cards
    * »  3.5 x 8.5 Rack Cards Printing
    * »  4 x 9 Rack Cards Printing
    * »  Custom Rack Cards
  * »  Rolodex Cards
  * »  Stickers
    * »  Alarm Stickers
    * »  Anniversary Seals
    * »  Appointment Card Stickers
    * »  Asset Tags Printing
    * »  Bumper Stickers
    * »  Business Card Stickers
    * »  Danger Sign Stickers
    * »  Die Cut Sticker
    * »  Domed Labels and Stickers
    * »  Double Sided Stickers
    * »  Flourescent Stickers
    * »  Hang Tags
    * »  Hard Hat Stickers
    * »  Lapel Stickers
    * »  Outdoor Stickers
    * »  Paper Stickers
    * »  Parking Stickers and Tags
    * »  Postcards Sticker
    * »  Pro-Cut Vinyl Stickers
    * »  Rectangular Sticker
    * »  Round Sticker
    * »  Security Hologram
    * »  Static Clings
    * »  Tamper Evident Stickers
    * »  Thank You Stickers
    * »  Vinyl Stickers
    * »  Warning Stickers
    * »  Custom Stickers
  * »  Table Tents
    * »  2.8 x 11 Table Tents
    * »  4.25 x 5.5 Table Tents
    * »  Custom Table Tent
  * »  Tags
    * »  Asset Tags
    * »  Hang Tags
    * »  Parking Stickers and Tags
    * »  Swing Tags
  * »  Tickets
    * »  Standard Tickets
    * »  Jumbo Tickets
    * »  Custom Tickets
  * »  Vinyl Banners
    * »  10 oz Vinyl Banners
    * »  12 oz Vinyl Banners
    * »  Custom Vinyl Banner

| 

www.printingblue.com is committed to maintaining the confidentiality of our customers. We do not share, sell, or otherwise disclose information about our clients to any other party except as required to process and ship purchases.

Information Collection

Printingblue is the sole owner of the information collected on http://www.Printingblue.com. Printingblue collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

Registration

In order to use My Printingblue, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give a name and email address. We use this information to contact the user about our services even if they have not placed an order.

Order

We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for credit card authorization and to fill customers orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use persistent cookies. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

Cookies are used by both My Printingblue and the Printingblue order section in order to uniquely identify users, associate user files with orders, and to enable the shopping basket. Our site cannot be used with cookies turned off.

Log Files

Like most standard web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This data is not linked to personally identifiable information.

Communications from the Site

Special Offers and Updates

Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. If you do not wish to receive future emails, send an email to remove@Printingblue.com

Newsletter

Customers are automatically subscribed to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy, we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. If you do not wish to receive future newsletters, send an email to info@printingblue.com

Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services. Our production and customer service use both email and phone information to communicate with customers in regards to issues relating to in process order.

Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

Third Party Intermediaries

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

Business Transitions

If Printingblue goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. If as a result of the business transition, the users’ personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our order form has an ‘opt-out’ mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don’t want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at remove@Printingblue.com

Links

Our sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Security

Our Web sites take every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry—SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing.’

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Employees must enter their password to gain access to user information. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a high-security environment at our co-location facility.

Supplementation of Information

Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.

If customers have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change.

PrintingBlue is an American printing company providing the printing services to regular clients in USA and Canada. We have free design and free shipment services in all the state and cities of USA and canada including Stamford, Bellevue, Flint, Vallejo, Springfield, Evansville, Inglewood, Abilene, Olathe, Lansing, Lafayette, Provo, Visalia, Ann Arbor, Clarksville, Peoria, Cary, Athensa, Beaumont, Costa Mesa, Denton, Manchester, Independence, Downey, Thornton, Gainesville, Santa Clara, Miramar, Charleston, West Covina, Clearwater, McKinney, Allentown, Waterbury, Roseville, Westminster, Norwalk, South Bend, Fairfield, Arvada, Pompano Beach, Burbank, San Buenaventura, Pueblo, Lowell, Norman, Richmond, Midland, Erie, Killeen, Elgin, Berkeley, Portsmouthd, Cambridge, Daly City, Antioch, Green Bay, West Jordane, Billings, Carson, Lynn, Port St. Lucie, Vacaville, San Angelo, Sandy, Westminster, Quincy, Miami Beach, Waukegan, Duluth, Killeen, Nashua, Westland, High Point, Warwick, Rochester, Alhambra, Sunrise, Parma, Cicero town, Trenton, Bloomington, Citrus Heights, Sioux, Columbia, Orem, Hawthorne, Santa Monica, Newton, Whittier, Tyler, Federal Way, Hammond, Norwalk, Plantation, Thornton, Farmington Hills, West Palm Beach, Youngstown, Decatur, Racine, Reading, Troy, Redding, Canton, Denton, Fort Smith, Lawrence, Roseville, Camden. 

Contact Information

If customers have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Customer Service   
P.O. BOX 281  
Streamwood, IL 60107-0281  
Telephone: 302-356-1432**
